<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Benedict Wilkins</title>
    <link>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Benedict Wilkins</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 11:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect 4 Gym</title>
      <link>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/post/connect4-gym/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 11:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/post/connect4-gym/</guid>
      <description>My goal is to completely solve the game of Connect4 (also sometimes called Four in a row). By completely, I mean completely. Essentially, I am going to go through all the steps in making a fully functional connect 4 robot that can play a physical game, and yes that includes building a robotic arm, a vision system, a learning algorithm that will enable our agent to learn to play from scratch, and everything else in between that is needed to tie it all together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conway&#39;s Game of Life</title>
      <link>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/post/gameoflife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 11:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/post/gameoflife/</guid>
      <description>First in a series of mini-projects. The famous game of life originally conceived by the late John Conway is a fascinating example of a [Cellular Automaton][https://mathworld.wolfram.com/CellularAutomaton.html] (of which there are many). The game of life is often given as a homework task to undergraduate students in introductory programming courses &amp;ndash; if this is you I encourage you to look deeper into the motivation behind the conception of the game of life, or simply Life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siamese Networks</title>
      <link>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/post/siamese-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/post/siamese-networks/</guid>
      <description>Recently I have been looking into Siamese networks in my research, for my own understanding I like to implement new models that I come across - if you can code it you must understand it! Lets begin.
What is a Siamese Network? There are some great resources on the web that answer this question, in particular this short course by distinguished researcher Andrew Ng. For completeness I will explain the idea briefly here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial: Multi-threading and tkinter</title>
      <link>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/post/tkinter-mp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 18:08:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benedictwilkinsai.github.io/post/tkinter-mp/</guid>
      <description>On occasion in my work I need a visualisation that gives a bit more than what pyplot can provide. tkinter was an obvious choice as a fairly powerful pure python GUI library it has (almost) everything one might need for simple interactive interfaces. As always, and with little to no understanding of the library I jumped straight in and tried to develop a super complicated GUI for a project I have been working on called vacuumworld.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>